<xbel version="1.0">
    <title>Bookmarks from David</title>
    <folder>
        <title>Food</title>
        <folder>
            <title>Tea</title>
            <bookmark href="http://www.uptontea.com/">
                <title>Upton Tea Imports</title>
                <desc>Upton Tea Imports was founded in 1989 with the objective of providing the
                    North American tea drinker with the finest teas available. We purchase teas from
                    reputable brokers and estates worldwide, dealing only with sources who are
                    capable of providing top quality teas. We sell directly to the consumer, thus
                    ensuring the freshest product and fairest pricing.</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.tealuxe.com/">
                <title>Tealuxe</title>
                <desc>Located at Zero Brattle St. Tealuxe began in Harvard Square in 1996. Tall
                    ceilings, dark woods, copper table-tops, and vintage jazz create the setting;
                    the smell of over 100 teas and jovial conversation create the atmosphere. We
                    hope you enjoy your Tealuxe tea as much as we do.</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.dadotea.com/">
                <title>Dado Tea</title>
                <desc>50 Church St and 955 Massachusetts Ave in Cambridge. Dado Tea is owned and
                    operated locally. It seeks to serve healthy food that nourishes the mind and
                    body of its customers.</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://memteaimports.com/">
                <title>MEM Tea Imports</title>
                <desc>MEM Tea Imports is located in Somerville, MA. Its teas are available at many
                    restaurants, including Crema Cafe. Its loose-leaf teas can be purchased in
                    packets for home at Cardullo's Gourmet Shoppe.</desc>
            </bookmark>
        </folder>
        <folder>
            <title>Spices and Herbs</title>
            <bookmark href="http://www.penzeys.com/">
                <title>Penzeys Spices</title>
                <desc>See why our unmatched quality, abundant variety, and love of everyone who
                    cooks have made us the top on-line seller of spices. Penzeys for great flavor
                    everyday.</desc>
            </bookmark>
        </folder>
        <folder>
            <title>Chips</title>
            <bookmark href="http://www.dirtys.com/">
                <title>Dirty Potato Chips</title>
                <desc>At "Dirty's" we don't wash out the natural potato flavor, so our chips are
                    crunchier and tastier. Enjoy - John Shaw, Chip Master</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.artsandmarys.com/">
                <title>Art's and Mary's: Homestyle Tater Chips</title>
                <desc>At Art's and Mary's, we understand Americans' desire for potato chips that are
                    more that just another snack. When they want to treat themselves to something
                    special, they appreciate a chip that's cut thick and bursting with bold flavor.
                    That's why they pass up all those ordinary chips and pick up a bag of Art's and
                    Mary's. After all...Why Eat the Ordinary?</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.timschips.com/">
                <title>Tim's Cascade Style Potato Chips</title>
                <desc>Tim's has been creating our famous chips in the shadow of the Cascade Mountain
                    range since 1986 using an old family recipe. By starting with premium potatoes
                    direct from family owned farms and only the finest blends of real seasonings, we
                    think you'll agree that you have discovered what you have been looking for from
                    your first satisfying crunch</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.capecodchips.com/">
                <title>Cape Cod Potato Chips</title>
                <desc>For over 25 years, Cape Cod Potato Chips has brought you all-natural goodness
                    and fresh flavors with our hand-stirred kettle-cooked chips. The legendary
                    crunch of our chips have made them a classic on the Cape and around the
                    world.</desc>
            </bookmark>
        </folder>
        <folder>
            <title>Lunch in Harvard Square</title>
            <bookmark href="http://www.pinocchiospizza.net/">
                <title>Pinocchio's Pizza &amp; Subs</title>
                <desc>74 Winthrop St. Noch's has been serving up great pizza and subs to Harvard
                    University students for over 30 years. Come to Pinocchio's and have the best
                    slices of Sicilian pizza and mouth-watering steak sandwiches!</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.felipestaqueria.com/">
                <title>Felipe's Taqueria</title>
                <desc>Felipe's Taqueria serves authentic Mexican food to the Cambrdige and Boston
                    area. Our menu, contact information, location, and catering information are all
                    listed here at Felipes Taqueria website. We also cater Mexican and Latin food to
                    Boston, Massachusetts.</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.cremacambridge.com/">
                <title>Crema Cafe</title>
                <desc>27 Brattle St. At Crema you can meet, chat, sip, read, write, watch, think,
                    taste and enjoy in an atmosphere that you simultaneously create and absorb. Our
                    goal is for Crema to be a familiar, warm nook in the world where you can enjoy
                    some of the best things in life Â a delicious cup of coffee or tea, homemade
                    baked goods straight from the oven, and yummy fresh food in a environment with
                    both stimulating conversation and calm quiet.</desc>
            </bookmark>
            <bookmark href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/falafel-corner-cambridge">
                <title>Falafel Corner</title>
                <desc>A great place for falafel and more!</desc>
            </bookmark>
        </folder>
    </folder>
    <folder>
        <title>Web Browsers / HTTP Clients</title>
        <bookmark href="http://browsehappy.com/">
            <title>Browse Happy</title>
            <desc>Online. Worry-free. Upgrade your browser today!</desc>
        </bookmark>
        <bookmark href="http://www.mozilla.com/firefox/">
            <title>Firefox</title>
            <desc>Firefox Browser - Free ways to customize your Internet</desc>
        </bookmark>
        <bookmark href="http://www.google.com/chrome">
            <title>Google Chrome</title>
            <desc>Google Chrome is a browser that combines a minimal design with sophisticated
                technology to make the web faster, safer, and easier.</desc>
        </bookmark>
        <bookmark href="http://www.microsoft.com/ie/">
            <title>Microsoft Internet Explorer</title>
            <desc>Find out whatÂs new with Internet Explorer 8 performance and security and privacy
                features that help protect against malware and other online threats</desc>
        </bookmark>
        <bookmark href="http://www.apple.com/safari/">
            <title>Apple - Safari</title>
            <desc>Safari for Mac and PC puts the emphasis on browsing not the browser. Innovative
                features make your experience on the web better than it ever was.</desc>
        </bookmark>
        <bookmark href="http://www.opera.com/">
            <title>Opera</title>
            <desc>The fastest browser on Earth is even faster. But that is not all. Use Opera Turbo
                to double your page-download speed on slow connections. Download Opera now and get
                more from the Web</desc>
        </bookmark>
    </folder>
</xbel>